

JIMSON MIRADOR

PRODUCT CONSULTANT

SKILLS

Leadership

3 Peat Head Cheerleader University of Santo Tomas

Client Management

Awarded best in Client Management Codeflux Inc.

AWARDS

Best in Client Management 2014 Codeflux Inc.

Thomasian Athlete Award 2014 University of Santo Tomas

Santo Domingo de Guzman Scholar 2011 - 2014

University of Santo Tomas

CONTACT ME

39A Don Alfredo Egea Street, Cubao Quezon City, Philippines 1111

+63 917 150 0589

jimson.jgmirador@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am a passionate, driven, and creative person with strong sense of dedication, and 5 years of progressive business knowledge and experience. I am aggressive in building new opportunities, resolving problems, securing client's trust, and engaging in strong relationship with business partners.

WORK EXPERIENCE

• **PRODUCT CONSULTANT** | 2017 - 2019 Cartronics Marketing

Spearhead the importation, and client acquisition of a Vehicle Tracking and Fleet Management Solution, which generated an estimated gross sales amounting to more than PHP 600,000.00 in less than 7 months from initial launch.

 FUNCTIONAL & UX/UI CONSULTANT | 2015 - 2017 Indra Philippines Inc.

Lead business consultant and product owner in projects and pre-sales involving mobility solutions. Translates business requirements into user stories and functional mockups. Produce documentations and requirements based on project and business needs. Familiarity in HR, MM, SRM, and Finance basic functions as requirement in SAP mobility project.

• BUSINESS SYSTEMS ANALYST | 2014 - 2015 Codeflux Inc.

Responsible for requirements gathering and analysis, documentation, and close coordination with project stakeholders for business requirements, design, implementation, testing, and deployment.

CERTIFICATION

- CONSTRUCTION PROJECT MGMT.
 Asia Institute of Management.
- INTRO TO BUSINESS ANALYSIS | May 2016 Indra Philippines Inc.
- INFORMATION GATHERING TECH | Dec 2015
 Processworks Groups

EDUCATION

BS INFORMATION SYSTEMS | 2009 - 2014 University of Santo Tomas